Finding Aid for the National Hispanic Media Coalition Subject Files PASC.0278
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Fist Fighter (part 1 of 1) - videotape, (1989 Feb) (Box 26, Folder 20)
  Restricted: Reference copy required for access.
- Florence Figueroa - letter to Los Angeles Times - ethnic casting, (1995 May 21) (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Florida Radio renewals - WYLF-FM, WTMI-FM, WPOW-FM, (1988-1989) (Box 29, Folder 3)
  Includes FCC petitions to deny for WPOW(FM) and WTMI (FM).
- Ford Foundation - denial for funding, (1997 Feb 3) (Box 11, Folder 25)
- Foro 22 - press release, (no date) (Box 24, Folder 13)
- Fox - foreign ownership investigation - clippings, legal documents, correspondence, (ca. 1994-1995) (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Fox (1 of 2) - Rainbow Broadcasting's FCC complaint against Fox - clippings, legal documents, correspondence, (ca. 1994-1995) (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Fox (2 of 2) - Rainbow Broadcasting's FCC complaint against Fox - clippings, legal documents, correspondence, (ca. 1994-1995) (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Fox depositions (1 of 2), (1995 Jan-Feb) (Box 1, Folder 31)
  Statements of Barry Diller, Michael Gardner, and Thomas Herwitz.
- Fox depositions (2 of 2), (1995 Jan-Feb) (Box 1, Folder 32)
  Statement of Rupert Murdoch.
- Fox/Rainbow - FCC related documents, (1992-1993) (Box 20, Folder 6)
- Fox/Rainbow - memo about FCC's decision on KTTV case, (1993 March 24) (Box 20, Folder 9)
- Fox/Rainbow - Rainbow's FCC motion to re-open record, (1992) (Box 20, Folder 5)
- Fox/Rainbow - related FCC documents, correspondence and clippings, (1993) (Box 20, Folder 3)
- Frank Moran - Latino Business Association press release - Hispanic Economic Summit, (1997 June-July) (Box 11, Folder 26)
- Fred Rogin - phone message, (1995 April 18) (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Frontera Magazine - press release with magazine information, (1996 Feb) (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Fundraiser (7/31 ) - Thank you letters, (1987 Aug) (Box 22, Folder 40)
- Fundraiser 10/14/94 - planning and follow-up materials, (1994) (Box 21, Folder 9)
- Fundraiser 7/30/94 - financial pledges, (1994) (Box 21, Folder 7)
- Fundraising 10/12 - list of financial pledges, (1994) (Box 21, Folder 8)
- Fundraising article - LA Times clipping, (no date) (Box 22, Folder 28)
- G.I. Forum - press release - Howard Stern boycott, (1995 April 7) (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Gala event letters - Impact Awards Gala planning materials, (1998) (Box 18, Folder 14)
  With invoices, accommodation information, reply letters, ticket sales, among others.
- Gema Pinon - complaint against ABC news This Week, (1997 March 18) (Box 11, Folder 29)
- General correspondence - HAMAS (National Hispanic Academy of Media Arts and Sciences), (1987) (Box 28, Folder 2)
- General correspondence - NHMC, (1987-1989) (Box 28, Folder 1)
- General correspondence - SAG (Screen Actors Guild) and AFTRA (American Federation of Television and Radio Artists), (1988 Feb 25) (Box 28, Folder 3)
- General correspondence - Trial and Error, (1988 April-June) (Box 28, Folder 4)
- General FCC information - clippings, (1987) (Box 21, Folder 21)
- General information KCBS, (1983-1987) (Box 22, Folder 6)
  With KCBS FCC application for license renewal.
- George Lopez - head shot, (no date) (Box 2, Folder 5)
- George Ramos - clipping, (1995 Oct 16) (Box 2, Folder 6)
- George Vradenburg - contact information, (1997) (Box 11, Folder 28)
- Gil Avila - list of film and television companies and organizations, (ca. 1996) (Box 6, Folder 12)
  With SAG (Screen Actros Guild) Diversity policy.
- Glauber Management Group - NHMC financial report Jan. 31, 1996-Dec. 31, 1996, (1997 Feb 1) (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Gloria Molina - Latino community complaints about their representation, (1996-1997) (Box 11, Folder 27)
  Including ABC/Disney and Howard Stern.
- Gloria Molina Speech - Los Angeles NHMC conference, (1987 April 24) (Box 23, Folder 14)
- Gloria Moraga - letters of complaint to the Daily Breeze, (1987) (Box 22, Folder 15)
- Graduation speech by unknown author - Eastern Puerto Rico University, (1999 June 8) (Box 17, Folder 5)
  Speech in Spanish - "Discurso de Ceremonia de Graduacion Colegio Universitario del Este Puerto Rico."
- Greater Media - correspondence - Howard Stern program, (1995 April-July) (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Green Lining Institute - request for NHMC organization Articles and Bylaws, (ca. 1996-1997) (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Gruber Murdoch - LA Times clipping, (1996 Dec 7) (Box 6, Folder 14)
- Guy Aioki - KFI's Bill Handel Show transcript, (ca. 1995) (Box 2, Folder 7)
  With list of Howard Stern advertisers pulling ads.
- HACR [Hispanic Association on Corporate Responsibility] - research studies, (1996-1997) (Box 11, Folder 30)
  Studies include: "The 1996 Study on Corporate Philanthropy," and "The 1996 HACR Study on Corporate Governance."
- Hadeishi Court Reporters (1 of 2) - copy of E.R. 1/15/91 FCC deposition, (1991 Jan 21) (Box 20, Folder 1)
- Hadeishi Court Reporters (2 of 2) - copy of E.R. 1/15/91 FCC deposition, (1991 Jan 21) (Box 20, Folder 2)
- Hallmark honoring Hispanic Media Professionals - clippings and program, (1987) (Box 22, Folder 11)
- HAMAS [National Hispanic Academy of Media Arts and Sciences] - news bulletin, (1997) (Box 11, Folder 31)
- Hector Castillo - complaint about NBC employment, (1997 Jan 17) (Box 11, Folder 32)
- Hector Flores - LULAC (League of United Latin American Citizens) Texas boycott of HEFTEL broadcasting and Howard Stern, (ca. 1995-1996) (Box 6, Folder 15)
- HFP (Hispanic Film Project) - Columbia College, (ca. 1989) (Box 24, Folder 14)
- HFP (Hispanic Film Project) 2nd annual competition - promotions and application drafts, (1988 - 1989) (Box 24, Folder 15)
- HISPA (Hispanic Association of AT&T Employees) - community leader meeting and organization information, (1995 Sept, Nov) (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Hispanic [Link] news services (D.C.) - Television and the Latino Child article by Frank Zuniga, (1987 June-July) (Box 23, Folder 5)
- Hispanic Advertising and Public Relations Firms - list, (1995 Dec) (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Hispanic Business - clippings, (1987) (Box 23, Folder 17)
- Hispanic Business - magazines and clippings, (1994-1998) (Box 2, Folder 14)
  With "100 Most Influential Hispanics in the U.S." questionnaire for A.N.
- Hispanic Business Association - letter in support of NHMC, (1997 Aug 7) (Box 11, Folder 34)
- Hispanic consumer advocates - membership meeting agenda, (1987 Oct 26) (Box 23, Folder 3)
- Hispanic Education and Media Group - organization information, (ca. 1994-1995) (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Hispanic Film Project - Screen Actors Guild communications for payments, (1998 - 1999) (Box 18, Folder 9)
  Hispanic Film Project: "Tanto Tiempo," "Always Roses," "Chavez Ravine," and "El Artista."
- Hispanic Heritage - letter of acknowledgement from White House to NHMC, (1996 Oct 18) (Box 6, Folder 17)
- Hispanic Link - clippings, (1987 July, Sept) (Box 23, Folder 18)
- Hispanic Media clippings, (1987) (Box 23, Folder 19)
- Hispanic media organizations - contact information and clippings, (1987) (Box 23, Folder 7)
- Hispanic Media studies - Strategy Research Corp study excerpt and USA Today clipping, (1986, 1987 July) (Box 23, Folder 21)
- Hispanic Media Update - newsletters, (1996 July-Dec) (Box 6, Folder 18)
  August newsletter not found in file. Also includes information on Heftel/Tichenor merger.
- Hispanic National Bar Association - organization information, (ca. 1995) (Box 2, Folder 11)
  With letter about Howard Stern boycott.
- Hispanic PAC (Political Action Committee) - organization information, (ca. 1994-1995) (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Hispanic Women's Corporation - 12th annual conference presenter information, (1997 Sept 5) (Box 11, Folder 35)
- Hispanic/Black - clipping and positions on CA ballot initiatives, (1994) (Box 21, Folder 6)
- Holocaust - LA Times clippings, (ca. 1996) (Box 6, Folder 19)
- HOPE (Hispanas Organized for Political Equality Education and Leadership) - newsletter and annual symposium programs, (ca. 1996-1997) (Box 6, Folder 20)
- Howard Stern - Chevrolet, (1995 April) (Box 31, Folder 7)
- Howard Stern - clippings, (ca. 1995-1997) (Box 11, Folder 36)
- Howard Stern - proposal titled: A Proposal for Dealing with the Howard Stern Phenomenon of Racist Broadcasting, (no date) (Box 31, Folder 10)
- Howard Stern - Resolutions against Howard Stern, (1995 April-May) (Box 31, Folder 9)
- Howard Stern - Selena clippings, (1995) (Box 31, Folder 5)
- Howard Stern - Sit and Sleep Boycott, (1995 April) (Box 31, Folder 6)
  Howard Stern advertiser picket. File may have been created by Alex Nogales.
- Howard Stern - TTMA (Texas Talent Musicians Association) support of Howard Stern boycott, (1995 April) (Box 31, Folder 8)
- Howard Stern Advertisers, (ca. 1995) (Box 3, Folder 1)
  See also Stern transcript in box 2 file 17.
- Howard Stern Advertisers, (ca. 1995) (Box 3, Folder 2)
  See also Stern transcription box 2 file 17.
- Howard Stern complaints, (1995 April, May) (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Howard Stern Transcript - Selena segment, (no date) (Box 2, Folder 17)
  See also Howard Stern.
- HPR (Hispanic Professional Roundtable) - newsletter, (1996 May) (Box 6, Folder 16)
- HPRA (Hispanic Public Relations Association) - A Proposal for Financial Support, (1985-1988) (Box 21, Folder 11)
  With HPRA Bylaws
- Hugo Chaviano - biography, (1997) (Box 11, Folder 37)
- IMAGEN - award publicity, (1998, 1996) (Box 6, Folder 21)
- Infinity Broadcasting - clippings and annual report, (ca. 1994-1996) (Box 6, Folder 23)
  Clippings about Howard Stern.
- Infinity Westinghouse - LA Times clipping, (1996 Nov 13) (Box 6, Folder 24)
- Information from the FCC to NHMC National Chapters and Board Members, (1999 Feb 11) (Box 18, Folder 11)
- Infrastructure [National Information Infrastructure Advisory Council] - report titled Common Ground: Fundamental Principles for the National Information Infrastructure, (1995 March) (Box 3, Folder 7)
- In-Kind Donations and Services - NHMC letters requesting donations, (1987-1988) (Box 22, Folder 26)
- Insurance [State Compensation Insurance Fund] - address confirmation, (1995 July) (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Invites - various event invitations to NHMC, (ca. 1996) (Box 6, Folder 22)
- Ira Zimmerman - letter of complaint about Howard Stern, (1996 April 30) (Box 6, Folder 25)
- Irma Lozano - file for Robert Beltran's biography, (1997 Nov 19) (Box 11, Folder 38)
- Issues Ohara [ABC], KCRW, etc. - letters of complaint, (1987) (Box 22, Folder 13)
- Jackie Guerra - Daily Variety clipping, (1994 Oct 28) (Box 19, Folder 19)
- Jaime Oaxaca - resignation from NHMC board, (1995 Sept 29) (Box 4, Folder 23)
- Jane Delgado - clippings, (1997) (Box 19, Folder 1)
  No videotape included.
- JAS Assets - promissory note, (1996 Jan 31) (Box 6, Folder 26)
- Jason C. Johnson - complaint email to Alex Nogales, (1997 Dec 13) (Box 11, Folder 39)
- Jeff Penichet - letter from Esther Renteria about NHMC dinner and seminar, (1998 Oct 15) (Box 16, Folder 21)
- Jeff Penichet - letter restructuring Hispanic Film Project, (1997 Feb 18) (Box 19, Folder 2)
- Jellybean Benitez - H.O.L.A. (Home of Latin Artists) - press release, (1995 Oct 19) (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Jeordon Legon - clipping, (1995 Feb 2) (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Jerry Tello - Cultural Issues and the Latino Population - executive training packet and information, (ca. 1995-1996) (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Jerry Velasco Nosotros - speaker information for NHMC retreat, (1999 May 7) (Box 18, Folder 1)
- Jerry Yaffe - research Hispanic employment in LA county, (1995 Feb 25) (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Jess Serano - Latino Advisory Committee - outreach letter to NHMC, (1996 June 12) (Box 6, Folder 27)
- Jesse Jackson - Rainbow Coalition research, (1997) (Box 19, Folder 3)
- Jim Estrada - letter about Howard Stern advertising, (1996 July 1) (Box 6, Folder 28)
- Jimmy Smits - Capital Style magazine, (1997 Oct) (Box 19, Folder 4)
- Joaquin Soto - invoice and resume, (1996 Feb 16) (Box 6, Folder 29)
- Job postings - CBS and PBS, (1999 June) (Box 17, Folder 4)
- Joe Castorena - opinion letters, (1996 Oct, Nov) (Box 6, Folder 30)
- Joe Dupont - complaint against Howard Stern, (ca. 1996) (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Joe Dupont - Howard Stern complaints, (1990-1997) (Box 19, Folder 5)
- Joe Hernandez -character reference letter, (1997 Feb) (Box 19, Folder 6)
- Joe Lopez - clippings and complaint against E and J Gallo winery, (1976-1997) (Box 18, Folder 23)
- Joe Ortiz - CCM (Chicanos for Creative Medicine) - information, (1995 Aug 25) (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Joe Sanchez - thank you card, (1995 July 19) (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Jones W. Cones - business plan, (1997 April 25) (Box 14, Folder 25)
- Jorge Mancillas - letter to Roland Hernandez (KVEA) about unionization dispute, (1997 Aug 11) (Box 18, Folder 24)
- Jose Chapa - event program honoring Chapa, (no date) (Box 18, Folder 25)
- Jose Luis Ruiz - letters, press release and ephemera, (1995-1997) (Box 19, Folder 7)
- Juan Munoz - development proposal, (1995 May) (Box 31, Folder 14)
- Juan Munoz AOL - Hispano Resources Center diversity training program overview, (ca. 1994) (Box 19, Folder 15)
- Juarez - videotape, (no date) (Box 26, Folder 21)
- Julia Silva - Tardeada fundraiser donation, (1997) (Box 18, Folder 22)
- Juliene Perez Gonzalez - complaint about Saturday Night Live, (1997) (Box 18, Folder 21)
- July 94 Fundraiser - NHMC invitation to Abraham Quintanilla, (1995) (Box 21, Folder 10)
- June 26th Sanchez's Pre-Fundraiser - planning materials, (1987) (Box 22, Folder 38)
- KABC - communication about Latino employment, (ca. 1987-1996) (Box 7, Folder 1)
  With correspondence, issues/programs reports, press releases, and clippings.
- KABC - correspondence from NHMC counsel about ABC's employment practices, (1987-1988) (Box 22, Folder 14)
- KABC - Radio-clippings, (ca. 1996-1998) (Box 7, Folder 2)
- KABC TV - press release, (1999 Feb 18) (Box 16, Folder 20)
- KABC TV - response letters to NHMC to improve Latino representation, status reports, and press releases, (1988-1997) (Box 19, Folder 9)
  Includes petition to deny license renewal for KABC(AM), KTZN(AM), KLOS(FM).
- KABC TV Agreement - Latino employment, (1993 Oct 29) (Box 19, Folder 8)
- KABC TV's issues and programs reports - fourth quarter 1998 and first quarter 1999, (1998-1999) (Box 16, Folder 26)
- KABC/KLOS - communication to and from NHMC, (1989 - 1990) (Box 27, Folder 7)
  With 1989 KABC/KLOS annual employment report.
- KACE FM Sunday morning interviews, (1995 May 21) (Box 3, Folder 6)
  With photographs for KLSX radio press conference (1995 July 14).
- Karen Watson - NHMC meeting planning materials, (1995 Nov) (Box 19, Folder 22)
- Kathleen O'Reilly - comments to FCC about Telecommunications Act of 1996, (1996 April 18) (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Katz - Jeff Katz and Chancellor Broadcasting - illegal immigration controversy, (1996 Aug) (Box 6, Folder 31)
  Mostly clippings and press release.
- KAVL - KAVS - NHMC's FCC petition to deny license renewal and annual employment reports, (1991-1997) (Box 18, Folder 27)
- KBIG - annual employment reports and equal opportunity policy, (1991-1997) (Box 18, Folder 28)
- KBZT FM - annual employment report, (1997) (Box 18, Folder 29)
- KCAL TV (1 of 2) - NHMC's FCC petitions to deny license renewal and transfer of control to Disney and FCC decision letter, (1993-1997) (Box 18, Folder 30)
- KCAL TV (2 of 2) - NHMC's petition to deny license renewal and appeal, clippings, KCAL programming information, (1995-1996) (Box 18, Folder 31)
- KCAL/Disney - Young Broadcasting purchase of KCAL - clippings and legal documents, (ca. 1996) (Box 6, Folder 36)
- KCAL-TV - NHMC's annotated FCC petition to deny license renewal, (no date) (Box 20, Folder 8)
- KCBS - notes and correspondence about NHMC and KCBS, (1994) (Box 23, Folder 27)
  Invitation to participate on television program "Profiles in Pride"
- KCBS TV - communication between NHMC and KCBS TV - Latino employment and representation, (1986-1989) (Box 29, Folder 2)
- KCBS-TV - correspondence and clippings about Latino employment, (ca. 1994-1997) (Box 6, Folder 32)
- KCET - Budget 1990 and NHMC FCC petition, (1988-1990) (Box 28, Folder 7)
- KCET - community outreach materials, (1987-1989) (Box 37, Folder 13)
- KCET - letter from US Department of Labor to Al Jerome - EEO (Equal Employment Opportunity) policies compliance, (1998 Aug 26) (Box 16, Folder 25)
- KCET TV - NHMC's petition to deny license renewal and employment information, (1988-1997) (Box 18, Folder 32)
- KCOP - Daily Variety clipping, (1995 Aug 8) (Box 7, Folder 10)
- KCRW Radio - NHMC FCC petition to deny license renewal, (1997) (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Ketchum Advertising - Beanditos commercial - request to NHMC for review, (1996 April-May) (Box 6, Folder 37)
- KEZY Radio - employment reports, (1990-1997) (Box 12, Folder 3)
  With Raul Moreno complaint against Donna Nordstrom.
- KFI Radio - complaint against Joe Crummey Show, (1994 May) (Box 23, Folder 28)
  "Joe Crummey tape" transcription dated 1994 March 24.
- KFI Radio - complaints and annual employment reports, (1990-1997) (Box 12, Folder 4)
  Annual employment reports for KACE (1990-1994,1997), KOST (1997), KRTO (1994-1997), KBOB (1990-1992).
- KFSG - annual employment report, (1997) (Box 12, Folder 5)
- KGTV - San Diego - letter of complaint and clipping, (1998-1999) (Box 16, Folder 22)
- KHJ Los Angeles - editorials, (1988) (Box 24, Folder 17)
- KHSL TV - FCC decision regarding petition to deny, (1994 Oct 12) (Box 19, Folder 10)
- KIEV - Broadcast equal employment opportunity report, (1990) (Box 24, Folder 18)
- KIFM - FM - annual employment report, (1997) (Box 12, Folder 6)
- KIIS FM - annual employment reports, (1991-1997) (Box 12, Folder 7)
- Kissee-Sandoval, Catherine J. - FCC inquiry regarding guideline promoting equal opportunity, (1994 April - May) (Box 23, Folder 29)
  Includes press release and notice of inquiry.
- KJLH Radio - annual employment reports from 1990-1997 (Box 12, Folder 2)
- KLAC AM and KZLA FM - annual employment reports, (1990-1997) (Box 12, Folder 9)
- KLCS TV - issues raised by NHMC, (1999 April 17) (Box 18, Folder 3)
- KLCS-TV - station manager selection campaign, (ca. 1995-1996) (Box 7, Folder 4)
- KLCS-TV - station manager selection campaign, (ca. 1995-1996) (Box 7, Folder 5)
- KLKX - annual employment report, (1996-1997) (Box 12, Folder 12)
- KLON FM - FCC opposition filing in response to NHMC petition to deny license renewal, (1997 Dec 3) (Box 12, Folder 11)
  With KLON's annual employment reports from 1989-1997.
- KLSX - FCC decision in response to NHMC petition to deny license renewal, (1999 May 17) (Box 18, Folder 4)
- KLSX Radio - clippings and ephemera related to Howard Stern boycott, (ca. 1995) (Box 3, Folder 14)
- KLSX/KRLA 395s - annual employment reports, (ca. 1993-1995) (Box 3, Folder 15)
  With NHMC letter regarding Howard Stern.
- KLVE FM Radio - clippings, (1995, 1997) (Box 12, Folder 8)
- KMEX - Daily Variety clipping, (1995 Aug 29) (Box 3, Folder 16)
- KMEX-TV 34 - press release, (1994 June) (Box 23, Folder 30)
- KMPC/KLIT - NHMC's FCC license renewal petition, (1995 March 15) (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Knowledge is Power - KPWR financial donation/grant to NHMC, (1999 Jan 28) (Box 18, Folder 16)
  See also B. 19 f. 13
- Knowledge is Power - organization information, (1997) (Box 18, Folder 26)
  See also B. 18 f. 16
- KOCE - FCC license renewal application, (1988 Sept 9) (Box 37, Folder 15)
- KPWR - Baka Boys advertising campaign, (ca. 1995-1996) (Box 7, Folder 6)
- KPWR [Emmis Broadcasting] Financials - information, (ca. 1994-1995) (Box 4, Folder 1)
- KPWR Grant - NHMC sensitivity training program, (1996) (Box 7, Folder 7)
- KRLA-KLSX - annual employment reports, (ca. 1991-1997) (Box 7, Folder 8)
- KRTH AM/KRTH FM - annual employment report, (1987) (Box 24, Folder 20)
- KSDO Radio - Broadcast equal employment opportunity report and handwritten notes, (1990) (Box 24, Folder 19)
- KSEE - thank you memo to NHMC, (1997 Dec 5) (Box 12, Folder 13)
- KSON - annual employment report, (1997) (Box 12, Folder 14)
- KTLA - TV, (1986, 1988) (Box 25, Folder 26)
- KTLA TV - handwritten note, (ca. 1999) (Box 16, Folder 24)
- KURS - San Diego radio - communication about request to relocate with FCC, (1998 Dec) (Box 16, Folder 23)
- KUTY - annual employment reports, (1993, 1996-1997) (Box 12, Folder 17)
- KVCR - annual employment reports, (1988-1997) (Box 12, Folder 15)
  With statistical data from Tomas Rivera Center 1997 report "Latinos in the Inland Empire."
- KVEA 52 - Los Angeles - press releases and clippings, (1990 Jan 11) (Box 25, Folder 27)
- KVEA TV - Coalition Pro-Justicia flyers supporting unionization (faxed copies), (1997) (Box 12, Folder 16)
- KWED - AM Seguin, Texas - Alphonso Rincon - letter of complaint with NHMC correspondence, (1987 Aug) (Box 22, Folder 16)
- LA Business Journal - clipping, (1987 Oct 5) (Box 23, Folder 16)
- LA Police Commission - letter to NHMC regarding diversity, (1997 March 27) (Box 12, Folder 19)
- La Prensa - clippings, (ca. 1995) (Box 4, Folder 6)
- LA School Board - letters from Richard Polanco to Victoria Castro - Superintendent position and Michael Eisner - Disney, (1996 -1997) (Box 7, Folder 11)
- LA Times - Latinos in the Pages of the LA Times: A Story of Neglect report with clippings, (1997) (Box 13, Folder 1)
- LA Times magazine - survey, (no date) (Box 23, Folder 22)
- LA TV stations - rankings of Latino employees, (1994) (Box 21, Folder 16)
- LABA (Latin American Bar Association) - letter about ABC, (1995 May 15) (Box 4, Folder 5)
- LACECA (LA City Employees Chicano Association) - 25th Anniversary invitation and information, (1996 March 15) (Box 6, Folder 33)
- Lalo Alcaraz - LA Weekly clipping, (1997 Aug 28) (Box 12, Folder 18)
- Lan[s]ing, Michigan - communication and various program transcripts related to WJXQ(FM) discriminatory action, (1994) (Box 21, Folder 13)
- Lansing - Nancy de la Rosa complaint against Michigan Department of Treasury, (1994) (Box 21, Folder 12)
- Lansing Michigan Trip - event materials including Civil Rights Commissions annual report and Higher Education report, (1989 Dec) (Box 21, Folder 15)
- Lansing, Michigan case - Reply of NHMC to Opposition to the Petition for Revocation of License [of WJXQ (FM)], (1995 Jan 25) (Box 21, Folder 14)
- Larry Merchant - complaint about his on-air comments, (1997 April) (Box 12, Folder 20)
- Latin American Civic Association - communication, (ca. 1995) (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Latin Business Association and GTE California - corporate partnership statement, (no date) (Box 24, Folder 21)
- Latin Heat - monthly publications and conference materials, (1995-1997) (Box 12, Folder 26)
- Latino Association - request for NHMC organization information, (1997 April, June) (Box 12, Folder 21)
- Latino Caucus - list of Assembly [committee chairs], (no date) (Box 12, Folder 28)
- Latino Chamber of Commerce of Compton - board member list, (1989 Aug) (Box 26, Folder 1)
- Latino Coalition for Equal Representation - complaint against the Employment Development Department (EDD), (1997 Dec 20) (Box 12, Folder 22)
- Latino Committee on the Media - newsletter and 3rd annual conference program, (1988) (Box 37, Folder 11)
- Latino Student Assembly [USC] - Teach in information and invitation to Alex Nogales, (1996 Oct) (Box 6, Folder 35)
- Latino Summit - hand-out materials, (1995 Jan) (Box 6, Folder 34)
- Latino Workforce - US Merit Systems Protection Board report: Achieving a Representative Federal Workforce: Addressing the Barriers to Hispanic Participation, (1997 Sept) (Box 12, Folder 23)
  With additional information about Latino's representation in the media.
- Latinos for Social Justice - complaint against Herb Nero show and clippings, (1993) (Box 21, Folder 17)
- Latinos in television - research, (1998) (Box 17, Folder 13)
- Latinos in the Media - Cultural Issues and the Latino Population: A One-day Media Executives Training presented by Hispanic Media Association with Jerry Tello and Associates, (1996-1997) (Box 12, Folder 24)